<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<layout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">

    <data>
        <variable
            name="viewModel"
            type="com.example.pokemon.detail.DetailViewModel" />
    </data>

    <FrameLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:paddingHorizontal="16dp"
        android:paddingTop="16dp"
        tools:context=".detail.DetailFragment">

        <androidx.cardview.widget.CardView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            app:cardBackgroundColor="#00BCD4"
            app:cardCornerRadius="10dp"
            app:cardElevation="8dp">

            <androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                android:padding="8dp">

                <ImageView
                    android:id="@+id/imageView"
                    android:layout_width="170dp"
                    android:layout_height="170dp"
                    app:imageUrl="@{viewModel.detailProperty.sprites.other.officialArtwork.frontDefault}"
                    app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
                    app:layout_constraintHorizontal_bias="0.5"
                    app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
                    app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
                    tools:srcCompat="@tools:sample/avatars" />

                <TextView
                    android:id="@+id/textView"
                    android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:layout_marginTop="8dp"
                    android:text="@{viewModel.detailProperty.name}"
                    app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="@+id/imageView"
                    app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="@+id/imageView"
                    app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@+id/imageView"
                    tools:text="TextView" />

                <TextView
                    android:id="@+id/textView2"
                    android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:layout_margin="8dp"
                    android:text="@{String.valueOf(viewModel.detailProperty.pokemonId)}"
                    android:textSize="20sp"
                    android:textStyle="bold"
                    app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
                    app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
                    tools:text="id" />

                <ScrollView
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:layout_marginTop="8dp"
                    app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
                    app:layout_constraintHorizontal_bias="0.5"
                    app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
                    app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@+id/textView">

                    <TextView
                        android:id="@+id/textView3"
                        android:layout_width="match_parent"
                        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                        android:text="Run the app and select a property to see its details. Now you can see how much it costs, and if it's for sale or rent, to help you better decide whether a permanent move to Mars is in your future...  If you get stuck, go back and watch the video again. Once you’re done, you can check your solution against the solution we’ve provided herRun the app and select a property to see its details. Now you can see how much it costs, and if it's for sale or rent, to help you better decide whether a permanent move to Mars is in your future...  If you get stuck, go back and watch the video again. Once you’re done, you can check your solution against the solution we’ve provided herRun the app and select a property to see its details. Now you can see how much it costs, and if it's for sale or rent, to help you better decide whether a permanent move to Mars is in your future...  If you get stuck, go back and watch the video again. Once you’re done, you can check your solution against the solution we’ve provided herRun the app and select a property to see its details. Now you can see how much it costs, and if it's for sale or rent, to help you better decide whether a permanent move to Mars is in your future...  If you get stuck, go back and watch the video again. Once you’re done, you can check your solution against the solution we’ve provided herRun the app and select a property to see its details. Now you can see how much it costs, and if it's for sale or rent, to help you better decide whether a permanent move to Mars is in your future...  If you get stuck, go back and watch the video again. Once you’re done, you can check your solution against the solution we’ve provided herRun the app and select a property to see its details. Now you can see how much it costs, and if it's for sale or rent, to help you better decide whether a permanent move to Mars is in your future...  If you get stuck, go back and watch the video again. Once you’re done, you can check your solution against the solution we’ve provided herRun the app and select a property to see its details. Now you can see how much it costs, and if it's for sale or rent, to help you better decide whether a permanent move to Mars is in your future...  If you get stuck, go back and watch the video again. Once you’re done, you can check your solution against the solution we’ve provided herRun the app and select a property to see its details. Now you can see how much it costs, and if it's for sale or rent, to help you better decide whether a permanent move to Mars is in your future...  If you get stuck, go back and watch the video again. Once you’re done, you can check your solution against the solution we’ve provided her"
                        android:textSize="24sp" />
                </ScrollView>
            </androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>
        </androidx.cardview.widget.CardView>

    </FrameLayout>
</layout>